aseaglobal.com 2019-07-22

# Privacy Policy - ASEA Global | US

The following is the privacy policy of the ASEA GLOBAL, LLC – 1488 West Pleasant View Drive, Pleasant Grove, UT 84062, United States of America, represented by Managing Director Jarom Webb, located in Europe as ASEA SERVICES EUROPE GmbH, Lyonel-Feininger-Straße 28, 80807 Munich (hereinafter: ASEA), Phone: +49 800-7236606 Fax: +001 801-618-3955 E-mail: support@aseaglobal.com

You can contact our data protection officer, SBS Data Protect GmbH, at nori@sbs-data.de or at +49 40 73 44 086 – 20 For the assertion of rights within the scope of data protection or for questions regarding the use, collection or processing of your personal data, please contact:

Michael Auras

As the body responsible under applicable data protection law, we undertake to protect our customers’ personal data and privacy and to treat them confidentially. The collection, storage, modification, transmission, blocking, deletion and use of your personal data is carried out on the basis of the applicable legal provisions, in particular the Basic Data Protection Ordinance.

Your data is protected by technical and organizational security measures against access by unauthorized persons, accidental or intentional manipulation, destruction and loss.

### Access Data

You can visit our website anonymously. Every time you access our website your internet browser transmits the following standard data to our web server: the date and time of access, the sender’s IP address, the requested resource (URL, file download, etc.), the http method and the http user agent header. However, our web server stores this data separately from other data; it is not possible for us to assign this data to a specific person. After anonymous evaluation for statistical purposes, this data is deleted immediately.

We store this information for a period of 12 months. The evaluation of the data is in the legitimate interest of ASEA to optimise our offer; the legal basis is Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f DSGVO.

### Collection and use of personal data for contact enquiries

In case of an inquiry to our contact e-mail address provided on the website or via the contact form provided, only the personal data provided by you will be collected and processed. The data transmitted by you in the context of an inquiry are raised, processed and used exclusively for the treatment of your request. This also includes enabling third parties to carry out services on our behalf, in particular logistical services. This includes, for example, passing on to the Internet service provider commissioned to provide our Internet presence Veracity Networks. In doing so, we observe the principle of data economy. We only disclose the data that is absolutely necessary for the specific processing. The data will continue to be used to communicate with you. Apart from this, we will not pass on your personal data to third parties without your explicit consent, which can be revoked at any time.

The basis for the processing is your consent. As a rule, we store the information provided for 2 years or until your consent is revoked. You can give a revocation with effect for the future at any time. To do so, please contact support@aseaglobal.com stating the information required for the assignment (e.g. e-mail address, contact period, etc.) or fill out the contact form again with this information.

### Collection of personal data within the scope of donations (advancinglife.org)

For the purpose of fulfilling the contract, the personal data of the donor are passed on to so-called contract processors such as web service providers (Aplos Software, LLC), payment service providers (WePay, Inc.) and the accounting department , insofar as this is necessary to fulfil the above-mentioned contractual obligations. They are obliged to act only in accordance with our instructions, i.e. for the execution of the contract. With the complete handling of the closed contract the data of the customer are deleted. Data that must be kept for tax or commercial law reasons will be blocked after the contract has been completed. These data will also be deleted after expiry of the legal periods. The data leave the territory of the EU and are transferred to the United States of America. The basis for this is the necessity within the framework of the concluded contract, Art. 49 para. 1 lit. b DSGVO.

The admission and processing takes place in the context of the closed contract between ASEA and the donor, legal basis is Art. 6 exp. 1 lit. b DSGVO. The legal basis for further storage for tax and commercial law reasons is the necessity according to the law, art. 6 para. 1 lit. c DSGVO.

Collection and use of personal data in newsletters If you consent to the dispatch of newsletters via our website, we collect and use your name and e-mail address as well as any other data provided voluntarily for the dispatch of a newsletter. The newsletter is used occasionally to draw attention to new products, services or campaigns. The data transmitted by you in the context of a contact inquiry are raised, processed and used exclusively for the dispatch of the newsletter. This also includes enabling third parties to perform services on our behalf, in particular of a technical nature. This includes, for example, passing on to the Internet service provider commissioned to make our Internet presence available. In doing so, we observe the principle of data economy. We only disclose the data that is absolutely necessary for the specific processing. Apart from this, we will not pass on your personal data without your consent.

The given consent (legal basis: Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a DSGVO) is revocable at any time with effect for the future. To do this, please contact support@aseaglobal.com, specifying the e-mail address to which the newsletter will be sent, or fill out a contact form with the relevant information.

We store and process the information provided within this framework until you withdraw your consent.

### Session Cookies

ASEA uses session cookies in order to be able to assign requests and requirements of the interested party. C session cookies enable ASEA to measure the frequency of page views and general navigation. Our session cookies are characterised by the fact that they are automatically deleted from your hard disk 60 minutes after setting the cookie. The session cookie is stored: Name: the cookie name; Content: the session ID that generated the accessed website; Domain: the accessed website; Send for: Any connection type. The session cookie does not affect your privacy. No data is read out and stored, only technical data generated by the system itself. The purpose of this session cookie data is to allow the website to be used correctly. Of course, you can refuse cookies at any time, provided your browser permits this. Please note that certain functions of this website, such as the ordering process, may not or only to a limited extent be used if your browser is set so that no session cookies (of our website) are accepted.

### Youtube-Plugin

This website contains a plugin of YouTube, belonging to Google Inc. located in San Bruno/California, USA. As soon as you visit pages of our website equipped with a YouTube plugin, a connection to the YouTube servers is established. The Youtube server is informed which special page of our website you have visited. If you are logged in to your YouTube account, you allow YouTube to associate your surfing behavior directly with your personal profile. You can cancel this assignment option if you log out of your account beforehand. For more information on YouTube’s collection and use of your data, please refer to YouTube’s privacy policy at www.youtube.com.

The purpose of the integration of the plugin is the optimal presentation of our offer for visitors and customers. This is in our legitimate interest, Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f DSGVO. Further processing or storage by ASEA does not take place.

### Privacy policy for the use and application of Google Analytics (with anonymisation function)

ASEA has integrated the component Google Analytics (with anonymisation function) on this website. Google Analytics is a web analytics service. Web analysis is the collection, collection and evaluation of data on the behaviour of visitors to Internet sites. A web analysis service collects, among other things, data on the website from which a person concerned has accessed a website (so-called referrer), which subpages of the website have been accessed or how often and for how long a subpage has been viewed. A web analysis is mainly used to optimize a website and for cost-benefit analysis of Internet advertising.

The Google Analytics component is operated by Google Inc, 1600 Amphitheatre Pkwy, Mountain View, CA 94043-1351, USA.

The data controller uses the suffix “_gat._anonymizeIp” for the web analysis via Google Analytics. By means of this addition, Google shortens and anonymizes the IP address of the Internet connection of the person concerned if access takes place from a member state of the European Union or from another state party to the Agreement on the European Economic Area.

The purpose of the Google Analytics component is to analyse the flow of visitors to our website. Google uses the data and information collected to evaluate the use of our website, among other things, to compile online reports for us that show the activities on our website and to provide other services in connection with the use of our website. Google Analytics places a cookie on the information technology system of the person concerned. By setting the cookie, Google is enabled to analyse the use of our website. Each time one of the individual pages of this website, which is operated by ASEA and on which a Google Analytics component has been integrated, the Internet browser on the information technology system of the person concerned is automatically prompted by the respective Google Analytics component to transmit data to Google for the purpose of online analysis. As part of this technical process, Google obtains knowledge of personal data, such as the IP address of the person concerned, which serves Google, among other things, to trace the origin of visitors and clicks and subsequently enable commission statements.

Cookies are used to store personal information, such as access time, the location from which access came and the frequency of visits to our website by the person concerned. Whenever you visit our website, this personal data, including the IP address of the Internet connection used by the person concerned, is transmitted to Google in the United States of America. This personal data is stored by Google in the United States of America. Google may disclose personal data collected through the technical process to third parties.

The person concerned can prevent the setting of cookies by our website at any time, as already described above, by means of an appropriate setting of the Internet browser used and thus permanently object to the setting of cookies . Such a setting of the Internet browser used would also prevent Google from placing a cookie on the information technology system of the person concerned. In addition, a cookie already set by Google Analytics can be deleted at any time via the Internet browser or other software programs.

Furthermore, it is possible for the person concerned to object to and prevent the collection of data generated by Google Analytics relating to the use of this website and the processing of this data by Google. To do this, the person concerned must download and install a browser add-on from the link https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout This browser add-on informs Google Analytics via JavaScript that no data and information on visits to websites may be transmitted to Google Analytics. The installation of the browser add-on is considered a contradiction by Google. If the person’s information technology system is deleted, formatted or reinstalled at a later time, the person concerned must reinstall the browser add-on to disable Google Analytics. If the browser add-on is uninstalled or deactivated by the person concerned or another person within their control, it is possible to reinstall or reactivate the browser add-on.

Further information and Google’s current privacy policy can be found at https://www.google.de/intl/de/policies/privacy/ and http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/de.html Google Analytics will be explained in more detail under this link https://www.google.com/intl/de_en/analytics/.

The processing within the framework of Google Analytics serves ASEA to measure and evaluate visitor flows on our website in order to obtain an exact overview of visitor numbers, usage interests and other relevant information for the design of the company structures and the website. This is in the legitimate interest of ASEA, Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f DSGVO.

### Person Affected Rights

You are entitled at any time and free of charge to request information on your data as well as the correction, deletion or blocking or transfer of the data to a body to be designated by you.

Furthermore, you can revoke your consent for processing processes with effect for the future at any time. If you require further information about the storage of your personal data or wish to exercise one of the rights mentioned, support is available at support@aseaglobal.com or the postal address of ASEA.

Furthermore, you have the right to complain at any time to the responsible supervisory authority about our processing. Your competent supervisory authority is that of your place of residence.

We hope that this information has helped you to exercise your rights. For more information about the privacy policy.

This site uses cookies and other tracking technologies to assist with navigation, to analyze the use of our products and services, and assist with our promotional and marketing efforts. Accept[Read more](https://aseaglobal.com/privacy-policy/)
